A Guide to the Correspondence and subject files of the Chancellor of the Virginia Community College System, 1964-2012
Library of Virginia
- Series VII: Correspondence and subject files [Accession 50877], 1988-2005., Extent: 15 cu. ft. (15 boxes). (Box 1-15)
  - 2003 April (Box 5)
  - 2003 May (Box 5)
  - 2003 July (Box 5)
  - 2003 September (Box 5)
  - Transfer initiative, 2003 (Box 5)
  - Equipment inventory, 2005 (Box 6)
  - Office of the Executive Vice Chancellor, 2005 (Box 6)
  - Executive Order No. 89, 2005 (Box 6)
  - Facilities Management Services, 2005 (Box 6)
  - Federal earmarks, 2005 (Box 6)
  - Federal legislation and updates, 2005 (Box 6)
  - Foundation for Virginia, 2005 (Box 6)
  - Funding opportunities from Dept. of Education, 2005 (Box 6)
  - Funding for Capital Outlay projects, 2005 (Box 6)
  - FEMA Pre-Disaster Mitigation Program, 2005 (Box 6)
  - Financial Systems Work Group Bearing Point, 2005 (Box 6)
  - General Assembly, 2005 (Box 6)
  - GPAC, 2005 (Box 6)
  - Office of the Governor, 2005 (Box 6)
  - Governor's Task Force on Workforce Development in the Construction Industry, 2005 (Box 6)
  - Grant Award, High Quality Health Care Providers, 2005 (Box 6)
  - Higher Education Funding Proposal, 2005 (Box 6)
  - Honorary Board of the Virginia Foundation for Community College Foundation, 2005 (Box 6)
  - House of Delegates, 2005 (Box 6)
  - Hurricane Katrina Relief, 2005 (Box 6)
  - Internal Campaign, 2005 (Box 6)
  - Intercollegiate Athletic Committee nominations, 2005 (Box 6)
  - Kathy Camper Memorial Scholarship, 2005 (Box 6)
  - Meeting ideas, 2005 (Box 6)
  - Middle College League, 2005 (Box 6)
  - Middle College event with Governor Warner, 2005 (Box 6)
  - Middle College, 2005 (Box 6)
  - New degree offering, 2005 (Box 6)
  - New releases, 2005-2006 (Box 6)
  - HJR 713, Workforce development, 2005 (Box 6)
  - HJR 122, Campus safety, 2005 (Box 6)
  - Higher Education Transition Policy Committee, 2005 (Box 6)
  - Higher education in Virginia, 2005 (Box 6)
  - Higher education restructuring dates of note, 2005 (Box 6)
  - Information Technology, Dept. of, 2005 (Box 6)
  - Institutional Advancement, Office of, 2005 (Box 6)
  - JLARC, 2005 (Box 6)
  - Local College Board members, 2004-2005 (Box 6)
  - Local Government, Commission on, 2005 (Box 6)
  - Lumina Foundation, 2005 (Box 6)
  - National Governor's Association of Policy Academy, 2005 (Box 6)
  - Chancellor's Task Force on Nursing Education, 2005 (Box 6)
  - Nursing Task Force, 2005 (Box 6)
  - Old Dominion University, 2005 (Box 6)
  - Part-time Tuition Assistance Program, 2005 (Box 6)
  - Partnership for language instruction with Court System, 2005 (Box 6)
  - Pathways Colleges and Legislative Delegations, 2005 (Box 6)
  - Planning and Budget, Dept. of, 2005 (Box 6)
  - Presidential salary report, 2005 (Box 6)
  - Presidents' budget proposal, 2005 (Box 6)
  - Presidents' certification, 2005 (Box 6)
  - Professional Development Committee, 2004-2005 (Box 6)
  - Academic services and research, 2002 (Box 7)
  - American Council on Education, 2002 (Box 7)
  - Advisory Council of Presidents, 2002 (Box 7)
  - Administration, Secretary of, 2002 (Box 7)
  - Attorney General, Office of, 2002 (Box 7)
  - Auditor of Public Accounts, 2002 (Box 7)
  - American Association of Community Colleges, 2002 (Box 7)
  - American Association of University Professors, 2002 (Box 7)
  - Controller, VCCS, 2002 (Box 7)
  - Capital Outlay Management, Bureau of, 2002 (Box 7)
  - Commerce and Trade, Secretary of, 2002 (Box 7)
  - Community Colleges' Foundation Board of Directors, 2002 (Box 7)
  - Comptroller, Office of, 2002 (Box 7)
  - Commission on Local Government, 2002 (Box 7)
  - Compact Paper, 2002 (Box 7)
  - Congressional Earmark Projects, 2002 (Box 7)
  - Congressional letters, 2002 (Box 7)
  - Cornell University, 2002 (Box 7)
  - Council of Presidents, 2002 (Box 7)
  - Distance Learning letters, 2002 (Box 7)
  - Education, Secretary of, 2002 (Box 7)
  - Education, Department of, 2002 (Box 7)
  - Education, U.S. Department of, 2002 (Box 7)
  - Energy Division, 2002 (Box 7)
  - Op Ed, 2002 (Box 7)
  - eVa, 2002 (Box 7)
  - Executive Order 6, 2002 (Box 7)
  - Financial and Administrative Services, 2002 (Box 7)
  - Facilities and Management Services, 2002 (Box 7)
  - Governor Gilmore's Proposed Budget, 2002 (Box 7)
  - General Assembly, 2002 (Box 7)
  - General Obligation Bond Campaign, 2002 (Box 7)
  - George Mason University, 2002 (Box 7)
  - GPAC, 2002 (Box 7)
  - General Services, Dept. of, 2002 (Box 7)
  - Governor's Office, 2002 (Box 7)
  - Governor's Budget, 2002 (Box 7)
  - Bond Campaign, 2002 (Box 7)
  - AAUP Tenure, 2000 (Box 8)
  - Academic Services and Research, Dept. of, 2000 (Box 8)
  - Administrative Services, Dept. of, 2000 (Box 8)
  - Disruptive Student Information, 2000 (Box 8)
  - Education, Dept. of, 2000 (Box 8)
  - Education, Secretary of, 2000 (Box 8)
  - Emergency Services, Dept. of, 2000 (Box 8)
  - General Assembly, 2000 (Box 8)
  - General Services, 2000 (Box 8)
  - Governor's Office, 2000 (Box 8)
  - House of Delegates, 2000 (Box 8)
  - Information Technology, Dept. of, 2000 (Box 8)
  - Instructional Technology, 2000 (Box 8)
  - Local Board Members, 2000 (Box 8)
  - Planning and Budget, Dept. of, 2000 (Box 8)
  - Presidential memorandum, 2000 (Box 8)
  - Statewide Workforce Training Council, 2000 (Box 8)
  - Technology, Secretary of, 2000 (Box 8)
  - VCCS Professional Development Program, 2000 (Box 8)
  - Workforce Development, 2000 (Box 8)
  - Blue Ridge Community College, 2001 (Box 9)
  - Danville Community College, 2001 (Box 9)
  - Germanna Community College, 2001 (Box 9)
  - J. Sargeant Reynolds Community College, 2001 (Box 9)
  - John Tyler Community College, 2001 (Box 9)
  - Lord Fairfax Community College, 2001 (Box 9)
  - Mountain Empire Community College, 2001 (Box 9)
  - Patrick Henry Community College, 2001 (Box 9)
  - Paul D. Camp Community College, 2001 (Box 9)
  - Southside Virginia Community College, 2001 (Box 9)
  - Southwest Virginia Community College, 2001 (Box 9)
  - Tidewater Community College, 2001 (Box 9)
  - Virginia Highlands Community College, 2001 (Box 9)
  - Wytheville Community College, 2001 (Box 9)
  - Academic Services and Research, Dept., 2001 (Box 9)
  - Administrative Services, Vice Chancellor, 2001 (Box 9)
  - Advisory Council of Presidents, 2001 (Box 9)
  - ACT, 2001 (Box 9)
  - AAUP, 2001 (Box 9)
  - Comptroller, Office of, 2001 (Box 9)
  - Commission on Local Government, 2001 (Box 9)
  - Controller, VCCS, 2001 (Box 9)
  - Council of Presidents, 2001 (Box 9)
  - Council of Higher Education, 2001 (Box 9)
  - Data Collection, Legislative Agenda, 2001 (Box 9)
  - House of Delegates, 2001 (Box 9)
  - e-Commerce, 2001 (Box 9)
  - Education Commission of the States, 2001 (Box 9)
  - Education, Dept. of, 2001 (Box 9)
  - Education, Secretary of, 2001 (Box 9)
  - Education, U.S. Dept. of, 2001 (Box 9)
  - Emergency Services, Dept. of, 2001 (Box 9)
  - Equal Employment Opportunity, 2001 (Box 9)
  - Facilities Management Services, Office of, 2001 (Box 9)
  - General Assembly, 2001 (Box 9)
  - Governor's Office, 2001 (Box 9)
  - May 2002 (Box 10)
  - June 2002 (Box 10)
  - October 2002 (Box 10)
  - November 2002 (Box 10)
  - December 2002 (Box 10)
  - Blue Ridge Community College, 2002 (Box 10)
  - Central Virginia Community College, 2002 (Box 10)
  - Dabney S. Lancaster Community College, 2002 (Box 10)
  - Danville Community College, 2002 (Box 10)
  - Eastern Shore Community College, 2002 (Box 10)
  - Germanna Community College, 2002 (Box 10)
  - J. Sargeant Reynolds Community College, 2002 (Box 10)
  - John Tyler Community College, 2002 (Box 10)
  - Lord Fairfax Community College, 2002 (Box 10)
  - Mountain Empire Community College, 2002 (Box 10)
  - New River Community College, 2002 (Box 10)
  - Northern Virginia Community College, 2002 (Box 10)
  - Patrick Henry Community College, 2002 (Box 10)
  - Paul D. Camp Community College, 2002 (Box 10)
  - Piedmont Community College, 2002 (Box 10)
  - Rappahannock Community College, 2002 (Box 10)
  - Southside Virginia Community College, 2002 (Box 10)
  - Southwest Virginia Community College, 2002 (Box 10)
  - Thomas Nelson Community College, 2002 (Box 10)
  - Tidewater Community College, 2002 (Box 10)
  - Virginia Highlands Community College, 2001 (Box 9)
  - Virginia Western Community College, 2002 (Box 10)
  - Wytheville Community College, 2002 (Box 10)
  - Blue Ridge Community College, 2003 (Box 10)
  - Central Virginia Community College, 2003 (Box 10)
  - Dabney S. Lancaster Community College, 2003 (Box 10)
  - Danville Community College, 2003 (Box 10)
  - Germanna Community College, 2003 (Box 10)
  - John Tyler Community College, 2003 (Box 10)
  - Mountain Empire Community College, 2003 (Box 10)
  - New River Community College, 2003 (Box 10)
  - Northern Virginia Community College, 2003 (Box 10)
  - Patrick Henry Community College, 2003 (Box 10)
  - Paul D. Camp Community College, 2003 (Box 10)
  - Piedmont Community College, 2003 (Box 10)
  - Southside Virginia Community College, 2003 (Box 10)
  - Southwest Virginia Community College, 2003 (Box 10)
  - Thomas Nelson Community College, 2003 (Box 10)
  - Tidewater Community College, 2003 (Box 10)
  - Virginia Highlands Community College, 2003 (Box 9)
  - Virginia Western Community College, 2003 (Box 10)
  - Academic services and research, 2003 (Box 11)
  - Administrative services, 2003 (Box 11)
  - Administration, Secretary of, 2003 (Box 11)
  - Advisory Council of Presidents, 2003 (Box 11)
  - American Association of Community Colleges, 2003 (Box 11)
  - ACT, 2003 (Box 11)
  - American Council on Education, 2003 (Box 11)
  - Association of Community College Trustees, 2003 (Box 11)
  - Attorney General, 2003 (Box 11)
  - Blackboard, 2003-2004 (Box 11)
  - Campus Works, 2003 (Box 11)
  - Center for Law and Social Policy, 2003 (Box 11)
  - College Authorization, 2003 (Box 11)
  - Commission on local government, 2003 (Box 11)
  - Commission on Technology and Science, 2003 (Box 11)
  - Community College Review, 2003 (Box 11)
  - Conditions of transfer, 2003 (Box 11)
  - Controller, VCCS, 2003 (Box 11)
  - Cross Talk, 2003 (Box 11)
  - Continuity of Operations Plans (COOP), 2003 (Box 11)
  - Council of Presidents, 2003 (Box 11)
  - Dual enrollment, 2003 (Box 11)
  - Effectiveness and Efficiency, 2003 (Box 11)
  - Executive Order 50, 2003 (Box 11)
  - Fees, 2003 (Box 11)
  - Education, Secretary of, 2003 (Box 11)
  - Education, US Dept. of, 2003 (Box 11)
  - Electronic Learning Services, 2003 (Box 11)
  - Emergency Management, Dept. of, 2003 (Box 11)
  - Engineering and Buildings, Division of, 2003 (Box 11)
  - Facilities Management Services, 2003 (Box 11)
  - Finance, Secretary of, 2003 (Box 11)
  - Economic Future of Virginia, 2003 (Box 11)
  - General Services, Dept. of, 2003 (Box 11)
  - George Mason University, 2003 (Box 11)
  - Governor, Office of, 2003 (Box 11)
  - Governor's Education for a Lifetime, 2003 (Box 11)
  - GPAC, 2003 (Box 11)
  - Heavy Equipment Program, SSVCC, 2003 (Box 11)
  - Homeland Security, 2003 (Box 11)
  - House of Delegates, 2003 (Box 11)
  - Human Resource Management, Division of, 2003 (Box 11)
  - Institute for Community College Development, SUNY, 2003 (Box 11)
  - Information Technology Services, 2003 (Box 11)
  - Information Technology Organization, 2003 (Box 11)
  - Jobs for VA Graduates, 2003 (Box 11)
  - JAC Contract, 2003 (Box 11)
  - JSRCC Program closing request, 2003 (Box 11)
  - Kellogg Foundation, 2003 (Box 11)
  - Kellogg grant, 2003 (Box 11)
  - Legislative Services, Division of, 2003 (Box 11)
  - Letters to House members re: Higher Education Act of 1965, 2003 (Box 11)
  - Local College Board Members, 2003 (Box 11)
  - Management Standards for the Institute of Higher Education in Virginia, 2003 (Box 11)
  - Mary Baldwin College, 2003 (Box 11)
  - McGuinness, Aims C., 2003 (Box 11)
  - National Council of State Directors of Community Colleges, 2003 (Box 11)
  - New Pathway to the Baccalaureate, 2003 (Box 11)
  - No Child Left Behind, 2003 (Box 11)
  - NCPEP Policy Audit meetings, 2003 (Box 11)
  - Packaging initiative, 2003 (Box 11)
  - Parking directives, 2003 (Box 11)
  - PeopleSoft, 2003 (Box 11)
  - Public relations, Office of, 2003 (Box 11)
  - RFP, 2003 (Box 12)
  - Research report, 2003 (Box 12)
  - SCHEV News on Enrollment, 2003 (Box 12)
  - Senate, Office of the, 2003 (Box 12)
  - Southern Regional Educational Board, 2003 (Box 12)
  - SREB, 2003 (Box 12)
  - State and Community colleges, 2003 (Box 12)
  - State Council's Plan, 2003 (Box 12)
  - State Council of Higher Education, 2003 (Box 12)
  - Student letters, 2003 (Box 12)
  - Task Force on Access, 2003 (Box 12)
  - Teacher Education Articulation Agreement, 2003 (Box 12)
  - Technology Council Appointments, 2003 (Box 12)
  - Transfer Task Force, 2003 (Box 12)
  - Transfer report to Sub-Committee on Education, 2003 (Box 12)
  - Treasury, Dept. of, 2003 (Box 12)
  - U.S. House of Representatives, 2003 (Box 12)
  - Virginia Career Education Foundation, 2003 (Box 12)
  - Virginia Commonwealth University, 2003 (Box 12)
  - VCCS Federal Requests, 2003 (Box 12)
  - Virginia Foundation for the Humanities, 2003 (Box 12)
  - Virginia Retirement System, 2003 (Box 12)
  - Vice Presidents of Finance conference, 2003 (Box 12)
  - VCCS Presidents, 2003 (Box 12)
  - Workforce Services, 2003 (Box 12)
  - Workforce Investment Act, 2003 (Box 12)
  - Academic Services and Research, Office of, 2004 (Box 12)
  - Allocation Model, 2004 (Box 12)
  - Appropriation Items, Military and Nursing, 2004 (Box 12)
  - Audit Exit, 2004 (Box 12)
  - Autism Coursework, 2004 (Box 12)
  - Bridges Learning System, 2004 (Box 12)
  - Career Coach Program, 2004 (Box 12)
  - Chancellor's Retreat, 2004 (Box 12)
  - Community College Survey, 2004 (Box 12)
  - Commission on Local Government, 2004 (Box 12)
  - Controller, Office of, 2004 (Box 12)
  - Council of Presidents, 2004 (Box 12)
  - Council on Virginia's Future, 2004 (Box 13)
  - Delegation of Authority from Secretary of Education, 2004 (Box 13)
  - Dental Hygiene Partnership, 2004 (Box 13)
  - Delegate Lease Authority, 2004 (Box 13)
  - Differential Tuition, 2004 (Box 13)
  - Education, Dept. of, 2004 (Box 13)
  - Education, Secretary of, 2004 (Box 13)
  - Emergency Management, Dept. of, 2004 (Box 13)
  - Endowment matching program, 2004 (Box 13)
  - Enrollment trends, 2004 (Box 13)
  - Executive Order #29 Small Businesses, 2004 (Box 13)
  - Executive Order #63 Commission on Higher Education, 2004 (Box 13)
  - Executive Order #75 Real Estate, 2004 (Box 13)
  - Executive Vice Chancellor, Office of, 2004 (Box 13)
  - Faculty release time, 2004 (Box 13)
  - Federal earmark, 2004 (Box 13)
  - Fellowship program, 2004 (Box 13)
  - Fiscal year, 2004 (Box 13)
  - Flag rules and regulations, 2004 (Box 13)
  - Foundation for Virginia, 2004 (Box 13)
  - Funding, 2004 (Box 13)
  - General Assembly, 2004 (Box 13)
  - George Mason University, 2004 (Box 13)
  - Governor's Office, 2004 (Box 13)
  - Graduation rate analysis, 2004 (Box 13)
  - FFV Grass roots organizer, 2004 (Box 13)
  - Harris Group, 2004 (Box 13)
  - Harvest Challenge, 2004 (Box 13)
  - Help Preserve Community College Title, 2004 (Box 13)
  - House Resolution 12, 2004 (Box 13)
  - Library of Virginia, 2004 (Box 13)
  - Local College Board Members, 2004 (Box 13)
  - Lumina Foundation conference call, 2004 (Box 13)
  - Management standards for Institutions of Higher Education, 2004 (Box 13)
  - Nursing, 2004 (Box 13)
  - Pilot program for CC Connection, 2004 (Box 13)
  - Presidential Salary increase, 2004 (Box 13)
  - Priorities for Higher Education, 2004 (Box 13)
  - Positive effects of Budget, 2004 (Box 13)
  - QET - JTCC, 2004 (Box 13)
  - Radio campaign, 2004 (Box 13)
  - Remedial evaluation, 2004 (Box 13)
  - Restructure of relationships, 2004 (Box 13)
  - Risk assessments, 2004 (Box 13)
  - Senate Finance Committee, 2004 (Box 13)
  - Smarthinking report, 2004 (Box 13)
  - Southeast Virginia initiative, 2004 (Box 13)
  - State Council of Higher Education, 2004 (Box 13)
  - Support letters for VCCS system office, 2004 (Box 13)
  - SWaM procurement, 2004 (Box 13)
  - Switcher program, 2004 (Box 13)
  - System Office Security, 2004 (Box 13)
  - Talking points for dateline goals, 2004 (Box 13)
  - Task Force to review rising costs of textbooks, 2004 (Box 13)
  - Tech - VCCS Taskforce, 2004 (Box 13)
  - Title II, 2004 (Box 13)
  - Title III, 2004 (Box 13)
  - Town meetings, 2004 (Box 13)
  - Transfer initiative, 2004 (Box 13)
  - Tuition differential, 2004 (Box 13)
  - Tuition file, 2004 (Box 13)
  - Tuition payment plan survey, 2004 (Box 13)
  - Undocumented aliens, 2004 (Box 13)
  - United States Senate, 2004 (Box 13)
  - Virginia Administrative Dispute Resolution Act, 2004 (Box 13)
  - Virginia Economic Developers Association (VEDA), 2004 (Box 13)
  - VRS Board Nominations, 2004 (Box 13)
  - Virginia Tech, 2004 (Box 13)
  - Virginia Workforce Council, 2004 (Box 13)
  - VITA Migration strategy, 2004 (Box 13)
  - Workforce Development Services, 2004 (Box 13)
  - YMCA, 2004 (Box 13)
  - Blue Ridge Community College, 2004 (Box 14)
  - Central Virginia Community College, 2004 (Box 14)
  - Dabney S. Lancaster Community College, 2004 (Box 14)
  - Danville Community College, 2004 (Box 14)
  - Eastern Shore Community College, 2004 (Box 14)
  - Germanna Community College, 2004 (Box 14)
  - J. Sargeant Reynolds Community College, 2004 (Box 14)
  - John Tyler Community College, 2004 (Box 14)
  - Lord Fairfax Community College, 2004 (Box 14)
  - Mountain Empire Community College, 2004 (Box 14)
  - Northern Virginia Community College, 2004 (Box 14)
  - Southside Virginia Community College, 2004 (Box 14)
  - Southwest Virginia Community College, 2004 (Box 14)
  - Thomas Nelson Community College, 2004 (Box 14)
  - Tidewater Community College, 2004 (Box 14)
  - Virginia Highlands Community College, 2004 (Box 14)
  - Virginia Western Community College, 2004 (Box 14)
  - Wytheville Community College, 2004 (Box 14)
  - Academic Services and Research, Office of, 2005 (Box 14)
  - Access expansion, 2005 (Box 14)
  - Access, 2005 (Box 14)
  - Leadership communique, 2005 (Box 14)
  - Academic Program review, 2005 (Box 14)
  - Administrative Services, Department of, 2005 (Box 14)
  - Administration, Secretary of, 2005 (Box 14)
  - Adult Education transition plan, 2005 (Box 14)
  - ACCT, 2005 (Box 14)
  - Aircraft use, 2005 (Box 14)
  - AIS timeline and governance structure, 2005 (Box 14)
  - Allocation model, 2005 (Box 14)
  - Alumni database research, 2005 (Box 14)
  - American Association of Community Colleges, 2005 (Box 14)
  - Annual retreat, Chancellor's, 2005 (Box 14)
  - Awards, 2005 (Box 14)
  - Budget amendment, 2005 (Box 14)
  - Chairman's award selection committee, 2005 (Box 14)
  - Chancellor's commonwealth professors, 2005 (Box 14)
  - Charter proposal, 2005 (Box 14)
  - CEO evaluations, 2005 (Box 14)
  - Career Coach, 2005 (Box 14)
  - CTE preliminary report, 2005 (Box 14)
  - Chancellor's Fellowship, 2005 (Box 14)
  - College fundraising, 2005 (Box 14)
  - Community based job training grants, 2005 (Box 14)
  - Construction trades Task Force, 2005 (Box 14)
  - Construction training request, 2005 (Box 14)
  - Concept paper, It's time to rethink adult basic education, 2005 (Box 14)
  - Controller, Office of, 2005 (Box 14)
  - Council of President's, 2005 (Box 14)
  - Council of Independent Colleges in Virginia, 2005 (Box 14)
  - Council on Virginia's Future, 2005 (Box 14)
  - Dept. of Education, 2005 (Box 14)
  - Dual enrollment, Developing policy manual, 2005 (Box 14)
  - DMV license plates, 2005 (Box 14)
  - Draft timeline regarding restructuring activities, 2005 (Box 14)
  - Donations, 2005 (Box 14)
  - File copies of letters, 2005 (Box 14)
  - Housing and Community Development, Dept. of, 2005 (Box 14)
  - HB 504, 2005 (Box 14)
  - Middle College, 2005 (Box 15)
  - P-16 Education College, 2005 (Box 15)
  - Regis University, 2005 (Box 15)
  - Restructuring legislation, 2005 (Box 15)
  - Regional Workforce Coordinators, 2005 (Box 15)
  - Radio campaign, 2005 (Box 15)
  - Radio coverage, 2005 (Box 15)
  - Project Lead the Way, 2005 (Box 15)
  - Salary, 2005 (Box 15)
  - Search Services and Retreat Services, 2005 (Box 15)
  - Senate Finance Education Sub-Committee, 2005 (Box 15)
  - Senate of Virginia, 2005 (Box 15)
  - SACS, 2005 (Box 15)
  - SJR 74, 2005 (Box 15)
  - State Council of Higher Education, 2005 (Box 15)
  - Tuition increase, 2005 (Box 15)
  - United State Senate, 2005 (Box 15)
  - US Dept. of Education grant award, 2005 (Box 15)
  - VCCA Creation, 2005 (Box 15)
  - VCCS Creative Solutions, 2005 (Box 15)
  - VCCS, Six year Capital Outlay Plan, 2005 (Box 15)
  - VBHEC, 2005 (Box 15)
  - VCCS Educational Assistance Policy, 2005 (Box 15)
  - Virginia Employment Commission, 2005 (Box 15)
  - VCCS Endowment Matching Program, 2005 (Box 15)
  - VCCS Enrollment, 2005 (Box 15)
  - Virginia Community College Transfer Scholarship Proposal, 2005 (Box 15)
  - Virginia Domicile, 2005 (Box 15)
  - Virginia Foundation for Community Colleges, 2005 (Box 15)
  - VCCS Policies, 2005 (Box 15)
  - Virginia Public Broadcasting Board Meeting, 2005 (Box 15)
  - Virginia Scorecard, 2005 (Box 15)
  - VCCS Security, 2005 (Box 15)
  - Virginia 21, 2005 (Box 15)
  - Virginia Workforce Council, 2005 (Box 15)
  - Workforce, 2005 (Box 15)
  - Blue Ridge Community College, 2005 (Box 15)
  - Dabney S. Lancaster Community College, 2005 (Box 15)
  - Danville Community College, 2005 (Box 15)
  - Germanna Community College, 2005 (Box 15)
  - J. Sargeant Reynolds Community College, 2005 (Box 15)
  - John Tyler Community College, 2005 (Box 15)
  - Lord Faifax Community College, 2005 (Box 15)
  - Northern Virginia Community College, 2005 (Box 15)
  - Patrick Henry Community College, 2005 (Box 15)
  - Piedmont Virginia Community College, 2005 (Box 15)
  - Southside Virginia Community College, 2005 (Box 15)
  - Southwest Virginia Community College, 2005 (Box 15)
  - Thomas Nelson Community College, 2005 (Box 15)
  - Tidewater Community College, 2005 (Box 15)
  - Virginia Highlands Community College, 2005 (Box 15)
- Series VIII: Correspondence and subject files, [Accession 51054], 1971-2007., Extent: 24 cu. ft. (24 boxes). (Box 1-24)
  - Chancellor Oliver, Biography and photographs (Box 1)
  - Previous Chancellor's photographs, 1970-1990 (Box 1)
  - Position papers, 1970 (Box 1)
  - Newspaper articles, 1971-1978 (Box 1)
  - Clearinghouse for Junior Colleges: Topical Paper Number 19, 1971 (Box 1)
  - Speech, Gordon Davies, 1977 (Box 1)
  - Newsletter: VCCS Pipeline, 1978-1979 (Box 1)
  - Report to the State Board of Community Colleges, 1980 (Box 1)
  - Newsppaer articles, 1981-1984 (Box 1)
  - Remarks by Chair of the Board at VCCS Annual meeting, 1982 (Box 1)
  - New Direction for Community Colleges, Maintaining Institutional Integrity, 1985 (Box 1)
  - Newspaper articles, 1984-1987 (Box 1)
  - VCCS Directions, 1987 (Box 1)
  - VCCS External Review of the Internal Audit, 1987 (Box 1)
  - Report of the impact on the VCCS of the Recommendations of the SCHEV Remedication Task Force, 1988 (Box 1)
  - Annual meeting, 1988 (Box 1)
  - Information on Honarary Degree, 1989 (Box 1)
  - Review of the Child Care Educaiton in the Virginia Communities, 1989 (Box 1)
  - Factors Accounting for the Development of the VCCS, 1989 (Box 1)
  - The Virginia Plan, 1989 (Box 1)
  - Report of the Chancellor's Task Force on the role of the VCCS in Economic Development, 1989 (Box 1)
  - Report of the Task Force on Continuing Educaiton and Non Credit Instruction, 1989 (Box 1)
  - Report of the VCCS Taks Force on Educational Telecommunications, 1989 (Box 1)
  - Survey of enrollment decision of VCCS Students, 1989 (Box 1)
  - Report of the Task Force studing the Education and Training of Day Care Personnel in the Commonwealth, 1989 (Box 1)